I thought you would come again to see Fapta Sosu.
Oh, I see. That nice-smelling and fluffy Hollow Child has been taken.
And so you need a part of Fapta to help.
Okay, if you fulfill our long-held promise, Fapta is willing.
Take whatever part of my body you wish.
Wh-what did you say? So what is this promise we made?
You forgot the promise, Sosu. But it's something Fapta can only ask of Reg.
That face. It's been in my memories before. It must have something to do with this promise.
Fapta, please. Can you remind me of what the promise is just one more time?
I'll do it. I just have to know what it is.
I don't want to force you to make some sort of sacrifice.
But instead, can you at least lend us some of your knowledge?
No need for that worry, Sosu.
Fapta will offer up anything if it's for the promise we made.
Come now. Together we will eradicate them all, Sosu.
Sometimes I wonder why we ever came to this place.
I wonder how things ever ended up like this.
The answers to such questions cannot be given to us from anyone.
Because we are here as a result of choices we made ourselves.
We alone must find those answers.
Everything's fine.
I gave everybody else some, too.
Regardless of what those answers might be.
Notice.
The End
Belov
Please, I beg you, Belov. Stop doing this to yourself.
I couldn't resist. I had my suspicions. I never thought something could be so delicious.
Willingly, I know when he both does.
Belov, stop it! Your eyes!
Oh, you're up.
Wazikyan, I can't get Belov to stop. Just look at him.
He'll be alright. He's one of the three sages.
He's far from alright! He's losing it!
Bwako. I'm gonna go see Iremui. Wanna go too?
That girl keeps getting bigger day by day. The children that she births are just about oh so big. She's given birth every day, even while you were sleeping.
Iremui. Your mother's here to see you.
Iremui had already lost her ability to speak. And despite her children only living for a day, she lovingly, oh so lovingly, embraced them. And she just kept giving birth to the next.
I beg you, Wazikyan. Please let them be together. At least while... while the babies are still alive.
You're still alive!
I really wish I could, you know. But while you were sleeping, there just wasn't enough to go around. Had to use the living ones too.
But then the symptoms from the pseudo-water started to diminish. I've discovered the degree of freshness seems to matter.
Because our wishes dwell within life, after all. It's a thing of beauty, isn't it? Just look at this sheen.
I don't waste a single bit of them, you know.
Wanna try? Cooking it?
Let go! Please be careful! You're still recovering.
I'm sorry, Iremui. I stood by and let you precious babies be taken to time. Why do I not just go insane?
Forgive me, Iremui. I'm so weak. And I... I couldn't choose between you and all the people who've given me life in this world.
But then, just standing by and watching as your wish continues, and gets taken from you.
I... can't do it. So I will go, wherever you go.
Your heartbeat...
If...
If... living in this state is what you wished for...
If... you have wishes you want fulfilled in the future...
If...
I...
I fear I might...
If...
I might once again...
If... I might once again...
Allow your dreams to be squandered...
If...
But...
I...
You're here, V 我是...
If...
unable to simply die.
I couldn't make even a single decision.
Although I longed to be punished,
I could think of no greater punishment than this.
I beg of you, please stop.
For some reason, I can't resist,
which makes this harder to bear.
Please, I can't do more.
Even in hell, people keep living.
It's why we have prayers and why we have lies.
By the time our new normal settled in,
Idomyui had stopped her shrieking.
Idomyui, Idomyui.
What's wrong?
The scar left by the egg.
There's something in there.
It is the Cradle of Desire.
Did it not shatter?
That's the second one, you know.
You see, when you fell ill before,
Idomyui grew weak as if she was responding to you.
And well, that's why I thought I would give her another one.
What are you... you're saying?
There's more of these wish-making things out there,
and it didn't seem like it was the first time
the IUs had seen one.
So, I had them look for more.
Truly, I'm glad that we made it in time.
Is... this really... what... what she...
Is this really what Idomyui wished for?
I mean, just look at her!
I... Idomyui!
What's wrong?
She's sympathizing with you.
The time has come.
Let's go and see Idomyui's true wish.
See it with our own eyes.
Where... where are you going?
A-ahhh!
A-ahhhh!
No!
That was gone!
Hey Lord, no!
I knew if we ever left the camp...
it'd be all over.
Dammit.
Stay close to Irimyui.
Yui, try not to get caught up in the fray.
Please, please, leave me behind.
I cannot do this.
You're indispensable, my friend.
You're noble and never got used to the suffering.
I'm sorry, but none of us will do.
She stopped.
What's going on?
Hey, Ayu.
Any idea what's in this place?
Negative.
It is a hidden location.
It is very close to the center of the chasm.
I see.
So she wasn't too fond of the shade, huh?
Ida Mui, what's the matter?
What's happening?
She's absorbing the creatures.
She's luring them in to try and eat them.
Looks like it's still not nearly enough.
Thank you.
Huh?
Please.
Please consume me.
I prolonged my miserable, fleeting life by taking what is near to you.
I have toughed out starvation and pain before, but I couldn't resist.
My pride, my convictions, were all gone.
I can't stay a human any longer.
I beg you.
Please punish me.
My bones, my wretched soul, every part of me, devour it all!
No!
Oh!
Oh, my love!
Look at that. He's taken on a new form. Look how beautiful he is.
Thank you for that, Belaf. I'm glad we made it in time.
Come, everyone. Let us offer up our bodies to our queen.
This is our sanctuary.
More valuable than gold. It's what we couldn't obtain, no matter how much we sought it.
It is our home.
Huh?
Um, Vuego?
I don't want this.
Huh?
I just can't believe that this is really what Ida Mui would have wished for.
Don't... Don't you think that maybe putting in the second egg is what did this to her?
Hmm. So, Vuego, tell me what it is you want to do.
It's... It's all so wrong.
I'm sorry. I should have done this a long time ago.
Vuego, if you were to leave her like this, Ida Mui's deepest wish would no longer be fulfilled.
Poor Ida Mui.
Ida Mui.
She'd most likely be sad, grow weak, and end up dying.
And so, if I die here today, all this pain goes away.
I'm sorry, Ida Mui, for being selfish.
The warm darkness is mine alone.
No one should endure it.
Is that a symptom of the Pseudo Water?
Wait, no.
No. He's... Used to cradle it himself.
No one can take her away from you.
Iram Yui is yours, Vuego.
You are inside Iram Yui's head.
You see, this is where you can have the deepest connection to her.
Wasu-kyon?
Yeah. Think it suits me?
A cradle of desire.
You used one for yourself, didn't you?
Yep. I already gave my body over to Iram Yui, though.
So this is just the remnants.
But why?
I mean, the interference units warned us.
They said adults should not use them.
Vuego, you might call me divinely possessed,
but I still must do whatever it takes.
You've witnessed it, right?
If you were this cursed pit,
what would you do for those who come here and do nothing but pray?
Vuego, I believe we have been gathered here.
I just know it.
That compass you brought with you,
I don't know why,
but the moment I saw it,
I felt homesick.
Even though we were forsaken and abandoned by our homelands?
The sentiment I felt
didn't come from any nostalgia for our homeland.
It's for something one couldn't have
no matter how much they yearned for it.
Something that will never come back.
Something that will never exist anywhere again.
It's a fragile, but deep longing for the impossible.
Homesickness.
For me, that villain was my friend.
Dear Iram Yui.
Yeah.
I'm sure the Great Pit will continue to call out,
hereafter and far into the future,
to those who keep striving to fulfill their longing.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What do you mean?
I speak of hope.
I must be going now.
Please watch over things from in here,
where Iram Yui's feelings reach you directly.
This place is where you belong.
In the darkness, I could sense faint signals.
Iram Yui swallowed everyone,
their flesh and their souls,
and they became a part of her.
Iram Yui had since lost her human intellect.
But no matter what was done to her,
she kept living with one and only one purpose.
She consumed it all and absorbed the power of the Golden City.
Wozu-kyan!
The second egg!
Look!
Well, I didn't see this coming.
And saw that no one would notice.
She secretly, oh so secretly,
attempted to fulfill her blessed wish.
Iram Yui, what you yearned for,
but could not have,
was homesickness.
A longing too fragile.
A longing too deep.
It was your love.
Your final child.
I was so grateful.
Even Yui,
that you didn't relent.
You didn't forgive a single thing.
You couldn't forgive any of this.
You bottled it up,
screaming inside.
I couldn't see what your child looked like,
but I could hear her.
In the regrets of her countless siblings,
I heard how your soul was imprisoned,
and how your flesh was turned into a place to live.
She was screaming out with her whole being.
Iram Yui,
until I met you,
there was something I'd always been looking for.
But then,
I didn't need to find it anymore.
I grew to love the warm darkness.
We're far beyond the yearning of home.
Deep within the true darkness,
there was a light that no one could see.
And thus,
not a single person could take hold of it.
That solitary princess born within the black.
I couldn't help but have hope.
Hope that you would be able to fulfill the wish inherited from your mother,
and that someday the curse would be lifted,
and you could find your very own wish,
and set out on a joyful journey.
Now,
a faint signal informs me
that these beings are the children who have returned,
and the children who were still to be born.
They are the children Iram Yui never got to call by name,
only the shapes of their souls.
You're a little one, aren't you?
I'll call you Kati, then.
It's all right.
No matter how many times it takes,
I vow to give each of you a name.
You're a bit warm to the touch, aren't you?
If you cannot sleep,
I will forever sing you lullabies.
In place of your mother,
you can no longer speak.
No matter how many times it takes,
children of gentle Iram Yui,
when you are scared and cannot sleep,
I shall sing to your calm,
and as many times as it takes,
I shall call your names.
I will not forget them.
I will not forget you.
No matter how many times it takes.
Truthfully speaking,
Iram Yui didn't have the strength left
to fully maintain the village,
because Fapta was the one who inherited the three eggs.
But you know,
with the activity here
and all the different visitors,
her value is immense,
and it's what keeps Iram Yui alive.
Right now, this village is much bigger
and more robust,
more than ever.
Uh, Valko?
What is it that Fapta plans to do?
To free her mother, of course.
And thus, destroy the village.
Now because of her nature,
she cannot pass through the membrane
into the village.
But she's been searching for a way in
this whole time.
Hey, so...
Huh?
Valko, can't you reason with her?
Riko, look at it this way.
If a foreigner you've never met
told you to just stop adventuring,
would you?
No way!
Well, there you go.
That's how Fapta feels.
And...
The princess's wish is Iram Yui's wish,
after all.
I couldn't stop her,
even if I wanted.
Hey, Valko,
what is it?
What is it that you yourself want to do?
Huh?
Hmm.
I think I...
only want one thing now.
Riko,
I don't want to forget
about my friend.
...
Thank you.